孩子们 2012年的开始实在有些疯狂
Kids, 2012 started out kind of crazy.
巴尼遇到一个叫奎恩的女孩
Barney met a girl named Quinn,
凯文悔婚了
Kevin unproposed to Robin,
我告诉罗宾
I told Robin...
我爱你 罗宾
I love you, Robin.
可是当我问她
When I asked if she
是否一样爱我的时候 她说
loved me back, she said...
不
No.
马修告诉罗宾
Marshall told Robin...
你得搬出去了
You got to move out.
罗宾就搬走了
And Robin did.
我再也不去她的卧室了 好桑心啊
I can't even open her bedroom door anymore.
我为啥这么多愁善感啊
Why do I have to be so sensitive?
我咋知道啊 哥们
I don't know, bro.
你看看我 像被奎恩那小妞勾了魂一样
Look at me and that Quinn chick.
你不会听到我碎碎念
You don't hear me prattling on
说她的微笑多么摄人心魄
about how beautiful her smile is,
说她的头发荡漾着蜜色光芒 如丝倾泻
how her hair is like a waterfall of honey-colored silk,
说她的眼睛深邃如海
how her eyes are like a warm South Sea
闪烁着落日般澄亮如金的神彩
kissed by the fire and gold of sunrise.
我都不记得她的样子了
I don't even remember what she looks like.
-哥们 你明显喜欢她  -你难道不能
-Dude, you obviously like her.  -Can't you read
推理的么 泰德
between the lines, Ted?
我显然是喜欢她啊
I obviously like her.
这事怎么会在我身上发生呢
How did this happen to me?
从何时开始 我变得这么伤感多情啊
When did I become such a gooey romantic?
我觉着吧 你应该
Look, I think it's healthy
真心的对待女人 而不是把她们看成玩意
that you have real feelings for a woman
这样比较健康向上
instead of just seeing her as an object.
换妞
Switch?
Sure.
可是 为什么是奎恩呢
But why Quinn?
你只是跟她睡了一觉
I mean, you spent one night with her,
而且她还有点卑鄙
and she was kind of mean.
我们有共鸣啊
We just connected.
情感上 心智上 精神上
Emotionally, intellectually, spiritually.
就是说 是灵肉一体呗
So, mind-blowing sex?
是灵肉一体啊
Mind-blowing sex!
那之后的一个小时 我简直目不交睫
For an hour afterwards, I couldn't uncross my eyes.
我一边看着她 一边回想跟她爱爱
Which was awesome, because when I went back for seconds,
像是跟双胞胎玩三P啊 矮油太爽了
it was like having a three-way with twins.
那给她打电话呗
So... call her.
要是能打 我早打了
I would if I knew how to get in touch with her,
我联系不上她啊 我要崩溃了
but I can't, and it's driving me crazy.
我眼目所及 全都是她
Everywhere I look, I see her.
她在街头漫步
I see her walking on the street;
她在商店购物
I see her shopping in the store;
她还在那跳钢管舞啊
I see her dancing on that pole.
我也看见她在跳钢管舞
I see her dancing on that pole, too.
额滴神啊 那就是奎恩
Oh, my God, that's Quinn.
先生们 有请卡玛
Gentlemen, give it up for Karma.
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第十八集
翻译:  邵小庚 47.4 园丁姐姐 Roy 爪爪 Sophie
后期: Cathy   校对: Cathy
HIMYM字幕组倾情奉献
真感谢你俩让我住这
I really appreciate you guys taking me in.
我是说
I mean,
现在我无家可归
I'm homeless,
而且和泰德之间还是不清不楚
things between me and Ted are still kind of weird.
能有朋友陪着我 感觉真好啊
So, it's nice to be around friends.
亲爱滴 你想呆多久都行
Well, stay as long as you want, sweetie.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
唔
Mm.
我给你准备了一本日记
Now, I got you a journal.
虽然听上去挺二的
I know this sounds lame,
但是写写心情 确实能帮你排解郁闷
but it really helps work through stuff to write about it.
喔
Oh.
亲爱的日记 弄死马修他妈的梦想
"Dear Diary. The fantasies of killing Marshall's mom
就快要实现了
"Have become more vivid.
-今天 我扒了她...  -啊喔
-Today, I scalped her with a .."  - Whoops,
这本是我的
that one's mine.
在这儿好好享受吧
You are going to have so much fun here.
噢 你们不用费心
Oh, guys, please, do not
非要给我找点乐子
feel like you have to keep me entertained.
哦 罗宾 要是你不想找乐子的话
Well, you shouldn't have come to East Meadow, Long Island,
那你就不该来东梅多的长岛哦
Robin, if you didn't want to be entertained.
真的么 我真心不觉着这地方有啥好玩的
Really? I didn't think there was a ton to do here.
很明显 某人没听说过
Oh, apparently, someone hasn't heard
尤宁代尔的袖珍博物馆
of the Uniondale Miniatures Museum.
你可以欣赏19世纪的顶针艺术
You'll come for the 19th century thimble art,
不过首先你就会被瓶盖上的荷兰大师吸引住
but you'll stay for the Dutch masters on bottle caps.
还有
Plus,
你可以跟东梅多野猫队的
you'll be bowling with two
两位创始人打保龄哦
charter members of the East Meadow Alley Cats.
我们队致力于
"We're a hot dog eating team
用打保龄的方法吃热狗
with a bowling problem."
这主意
Shirley
是雪莉想出来的
came up with that one.
她玩得很好哦
Great bowler, Shirley.
那天她得了280的高分哦
She hit 280 the other day.
可惜了 那个高分出现在她浴室的体重秤上
Unfortunately, that was on her bathroom scale.
罗宾搬走后
When Robin moved out,
我的生活就像她空空的房间一样
there was a hole in my life
变得空虚 寂寞
in the shape of an empty bedroom.
我找了个新消遣来填满它
I filled it with a new hobby.
你在我以前的屋里干啥呢
What are you doing in my old room?
这屋空荡荡的 搞得我异常沮丧
This room being empty was bumming me out,
所以我决定找点健康向上的活儿干
so I decided to do something healthy
然后我就不会再想你了
that would take my mind off you.
噢 在一个不通风的密室里
Well, nothing says healthy
闻着四十磅熏猪排的滚滚浓烟
like smoking 40 pounds of pork loin
臆想着跟你前女友的对话
in an unventilated room
这真是健康向上哦 亲
while having an imaginary conversation with your ex.
就凭这句话 烤猪排没你的份了
Just for that, you're not getting any.
我分不到烤猪排
I'm not getting any?
你是那个快被油烟熏熟的人
You're the one smoking your own meat.
我闪咯
Oh!
我该怎么处理奎恩这档子事儿啊
What am I gonna do about this Quinn thing?
我想再约她出来一次
I want to ask her out again,
但我又不知道该怎么面对她是个脱衣舞女这现状
but I don't know how I feel about her being a stripper.
你怎么会烦这个
Why would you have an issue with that?
我的意思是 你约会过重刑女犯 军火贩子
I mean, you've dated convicted felons, arms dealers...
选美妈妈
pageant moms.
嘿 我对奎恩这事儿可是真心的
Hey, Quinn is someone I might want to get serious with,
而不是装作能帮她四岁女儿获得儿童选美冠军的裁判
not just pretend to be a judge who can help her four year old clinch Little Miss Biloxi
蒂凡尼的妈妈真的很想让女儿夺冠
Tiffany's mom really wanted that tiara.
这是个拥有八百万人口的城市
In a city of eight million people,
仅仅是因为偶然 让你走进了那家她工作的俱乐部
you happened to walk into the club where she works?
或许就是命运
Maybe it's destiny.
不对 那个叫命运的舞女在马龙派许俱乐部跳舞
No, Destiny strips at The Melon Patch.
她们可都是人 泰德 尽量跟上我的节奏
They're people, Ted; try to keep them straight.
等一等
Wait a minute.
如果这就是命运呢
What if this is destiny?
我刚刚说的
I just said...
如果这是宇宙出于某种原因
What if the universe
将我们推向了彼此的人生道路呢
is throwing us in each other's path for some reason?
这差不多就是我刚刚
More or less exactly what I...
我不管你说了什么 这就是命运
I don't care what you say, this is destiny!
擦嘞 泰德
Damn it, Ted!
你为什么就是不能感受到爱情呢
Why can't you ever root for love?
嘿
Hey.
奎恩
Quinn...
不 听着
No, listen,
在这儿 我叫卡玛 明白
in here I'm Karma, okay?
明白
Got it.
嗯 看啊 卡玛
Uh, look, Karma,
我发誓
I swear
我从来没说过这些 但是
I never say crap like this, but...
我想也许苍天正在
I think maybe the universe
告诉我们一些事情
is telling us something.
你愿意再跟我出去约会一次么
You want to go out again?
哦 不好意思 我从来不和顾客约会的
I'm sorry, I don't date customers.
看在命运的份上呢
What about destiny?
我听说她去马龙派许俱乐部了啊
I heard she's over at The Melon Patch now.
不 我的意思是 老天爷希望我们俩之间能...
No, I mean like fate telling us that we're supposed to be...
哦 听着 巴尼
Oh, listen, Barney,
我的经理一直在给我眼色
my manager is really giving me the stink eye.
我必须得回去工作了
I have to get back to work.
好吧 等等 等一下
Okay, wait, wait.
如果我花钱雇你跳个舞呢
What if I pay for a dance?
这样的话
That way,
你的经理会很乐于此的
your manager's happy,
而且 这样我就能告诉你
and then I can to tell you
你为什么应该和我再去约会一次了
why you should go on another date with me.
我想我没理由不去啊
I guess there's no reason why not.
好的 首先 我们有很多相似点
Okay, first off, we have a lot in common.
比如
For example,
我们俩的工作都是靠
both of our jobs are largely financed
那些喝醉的亚洲阔佬的巨额资金支持的
by drunk Asian businessmen.
亲爱的日记
Dear Diary.
这是来到这个岛上的第四天
It is day four on this island,
这个本地人叫做 长岛 的地方
which the natives have dubbed "Long Island,"
之所以叫这个名字
perhaps referencing
大抵是因为在这个岛上 度日如年
how each hour here feels like it may never end.
目前为止 他们还是欢迎我的
So far, they have welcomed me
让我对他们那奇葩的生活略有所见
and given me a rare glimpse into their bizarre way of life.
如果说娱乐 对他们而言 就是桌面滑球
By "Entertainment," They mean table shuffle board,
手工活儿 或者其他完全没有任何激情的活动
macramé classes, and other non-stimulating activities
这些活动在曼哈顿
which are only used in Manhattan
都是用来戒毒和降低犯罪率的
to calm down drug addicts and the criminally insane.
他们那儿饭店的菜单上居然有图片
A preliterate society, their menus display pictures
好像身处史前社会
of the food they offer,
在餐厅吃饭的时候 一顿饭的功夫
everyone is forced to sing "Happy Birthday"
要被迫唱四五次生日快乐歌
four or five times a meal,
甜点竟然插了烟花
and dessert has fireworks in it.
在家里 莉莉马修总是套着
In their lairs, they often don a primitive shroud
裹尸布一样被称作"窝舒服"的披风
called a "Snugget," And it is not uncommon for them
而且晚上九点前上床对他们俩来说司空见惯
to go to sleep before 9 p.M.,
对夜晚
fearing, as they do,
他们表现的无比恐惧
the night.
还有日记 我认为写你真是愚蠢至极
Also Diary, I think writing in you is stupid,
但是你是莉莉给的礼物
but you were a gift from Lily,
而且现在她在看着我
and she's watching me right now.
伙计们 嗯 我不打算在这里留太久
Guys, um, I don't want to overstay my welcome,
而且帕瑞斯说可以接待我
and Patrice said that she would take me off your hands.
所以 你们有火车的时刻表么
So, do you have a train schedule or...
哦 是的
Oh, yeah,
但是 但是 额
um, but-but
火车出了点问题
there's a-a problem with the train.
老大老大的问题
Big, big problem.
有个
There was a...
- 罢工  - 一道闪电
- Strike.  - A lightning strike.
闪电击中了一个正在罢工的列车员
That hit one of the picketers who was on strike.
在一场雷雨中
During a thunderstorm.
再说了
Plus,
她可能并不希望你去
Yeah, she probably doesn't even want you there.
你们俩怎么这么神神叨叨的
You guys are being weird.
哦 哦
Oh! Oh!
哦 我的天呐 对不起 罗宾
Oh, my God, Robin, I am so sorry.
我会把这些拿去洗的
I'll throw these in the wash.
它们明天一早准干
They'll be dry and folded in the morning.
也有可能周末弄好
Or the weekend.
到时候咱们再好好谈谈你搬走的事情
And we can talk about you leaving then.
要不就永远别谈了
Or never.
等下 莉莉 为啥不
Wait, Lily, why don't...
差一刻钟就九点了 睡觉觉去喽
eight forty-five, time to hit the hay.
晚安咯
Good night!
那 泰德 你现在有啥
So Ted, what healthy,
强身健体充满理智的新爱好了
not-at-all-crazy activity are you up to now?
我之前迷恋过烤肉 但是我现在另有所爱了
I liked smoking meat, but now I've got a new passion:
木工
wood.
你确定你说了什么的 对吧
You hear these things that come out of your mouth, right?
之后我又回到了欲望之豹
So I went back to the Lusty Leopard.
你知道吗 巴尼
You know what, Barney?
我之前立下过不和客人约会的规矩的
I know I said I have a rule about not dating customers,
但是你有点说服我去
but you may have convinced me to...
可惜了
Oh.
音乐停了 我得走了
Song's over, I got to go.
等下 不对 我说服你干什么啊
Wait, no, what? Convinced you to what?
不好意思啊 可是经理的眼神好凶好凶的
I'm sorry, but manager's giving me the stink eye.
擦 找点事做啊 经理
Ugh, get a life, Manager.
你刚刚想说啥的
What were you saying?
就是 我刚刚想说
Well, I was going to say
那个 我觉得你啊 好迷人的
that I do find you very... charming.
又那么风趣
And funny...
还这么性感呢
and sexy.
而且 是智慧与激情完美结合的说
And exciting and smart.
知老夫者 莫过于君
You so get me.
巴尼 你知道吗
You know what, Barney?
这是人家第一次了啦
I have never done this before,
但是你实在是太太太特别了
but there's just something about you.
所以 我猜 我的答案是
So I guess my answer is...
真糟糕
Oh.
音乐又停了
The song's over.
天呐 快说完啊
Well, just finish the thought!
经理我好怕怕的呀 额滴神啊
But the manager. God,
我恨死经理了
I hate manager.
喏 给你钱 你的答案是
There. Your answer is...
也许我们需要深入了解对方
Maybe if we knew each other a little better.
自我介绍一下啊
Tell me about yourself.
那个 这个 告诉你些什么呢
Well, um, what can I tell you?
我 就是
I'm, um...
迷人 还有 风趣
charming and funny
性感 还有
and sexy and...
激情和智慧
exciting and smart.
是啊 小女子哪有拒绝的本事啊
Well, how can a girl say no to that?
要不我们
How about we...
出去 来
go out on...
一个 呃 就是
aaaaaaaaa...
就是 那个 呃
aaaaaa...
这些音乐时间太短了
Ugh, these songs are so short.
那么 你到底给了奎恩多少钱阿
Uh, how much exactly did you give Quinn?
八 九百 刀吧
Eight, nine hundred bucks,
还有我的劳力士表
plus whatever my Rolex is worth.
这个有点
Whoa.
我懂
I know.
泰德 我觉得我恋爱了
Ted, I think I'm in love.
奎恩就是在玩你呢
Quinn is totally playing you.
啥
What?
乱说
That's ridiculous.
如果她是在玩我的话
If she were playing me,
她会答应和我约会吗
why would she agree to go on a date with me?
你和其他那些臭男人不一样
You're different than the rest of these schlubs.
就只有这一次哦 我会打破我的规矩
This one time only, I'm going to break my rule.
我们明天出去玩吧
Let's go out tomorrow night.
好极了
Sweet!
噢 我去 我明天得上班 擦
Oh, shoot! I have to work tomorrow. Ugh!
要不 头脑风暴一下
Hey! Brainstorm!
如果我们就在这里幽会呢
What if we just have our date here,
说定了
It's a date.
这算哪门子约会 这只是
It's not a date, if you go
在脱衣舞夜总会的钱色交易而已
into a strip club and paying for lap dances.
如果不是约会 她怎么会说来四次送一次呢
If it's not a date, why'd she say, every fifth day was free?
因为这是欲望之豹在每周五晚上的
Because that's the Lusty Leopard's policy
优惠政策啊  连我都知道 奇了怪了
on Friday nights, and I'm so mad at you that I know that!
日记君
Dear Diary.
这是我到这个岛上的第六天
It is day six on this island,
我开始感觉我不是客人 而是被软禁起来了
and I begin to fear I am more captive than guest...
早安 亲爱的
Morning, sweetie.
门球主要是老年人的运动
准备好打门球了吗
Up for croquet?
嘿 对了 莉儿 我的衣服
Hey, uh, Lil, are you done
你洗好了没有 因为我还
washing my clothes yet? Because I...
噢 非常抱歉
Oh, I am so sorry.
你的衣服无意间混到了
Your clothes accidentally wound up in the bag
我要捐出去的袋子里
I donated to Goodwill.
你把我的衣服送走了
You gave away my clothes?
这个在东梅多还是蛮拉风的
They were a bit fancy for East Meadow.
大伙儿都盯着看呢
People were staring.
另外 我们还有一个多余的窝舒服哦
Besides, we have an extra Snugget.
试试看
Try it.
穿上试试 罗宾
Try it, Robin.
他们打算把我同化成他们那样 日记君
They're trying to make me one of them, Diary.
而且我开始后怕
And I begin to fear...
我可能还蛮喜欢的
I may like it!
我真不敢相信在这个脱衣舞夜总会里
I can't believe we're at a strip club,
最大的蠢蛋就是你啊
and the biggest boob in here is you.
这是个真正的约会 泰德
It's a real date, Ted.
而且很明显你还没看见大傻波的双峰呢
And clearly you haven't seen the DeSalvo twins.
喏 就是她
She's right over there.
巴尼 够大
Barney... Yowza!
你并不是在约会
You are not on a date.
好吧 去证明下
Okay, look, prove it.
去证明她不是在利用你
Prove that she's not just taking advantage of you.
把她带到别的地方去
Get her to go out with you anywhere but here.
好吧
Fine!
嗨 帅哥 想看我跳个舞吗
Hey, sexy! You want a dance?
好啊
Yeah!
但是 有件事我得说下
Uh, one thing, though.
你不会介意
Um, you'd be okay with us having a date
我们去别的地方约会 对吧
somewhere besides here, wouldn't you?
我一直在等你这句话呢
I was hoping you would ask that.
真抱歉哟 虽然这里有点小贵
I'm sorry it's so expensive in here,
但是既漂亮又私密哟 对吧
but it's nice and private, huh?
当然啦 还超浪漫呢
Absolutely. And romantic!
这可是我们俩第一次单独约会呢
It's our first getaway as a couple!
亲爱的日记 有一个念头变得越来越清晰了
It's become clear to me, Diary,
那就是 我必须上演一场逃亡大戏
that I must attempt a dramatic escape.
我会在晚餐的时候假装胃疼
I will fake a stomach ache during dinner.
在马修和莉莉去渡宾果之夜以后
Then, after Marshall and Lily leave for bingo night,
我会溜到后门
I will sneak out the back.
去偷雪莉的滑轮车 再开去车站
I'll swipe Shirley's Rascal and drive to the train station.
顺便说一下 她都42了居然还骑滑轮车
Shirley's 42, by the way, and rides a Rascal.
我敢说 这儿的人跟机器人总动员里的一样退化了
I swear, it's the second half of Wall-E out here.
抓到你了
Bingo...
宾果之夜取消了
was canceled.
嗨 帅哥 想看我跳舞吗
Hey, sexy, you want a dance?
不 我不是来玩的
No, I'm not a customer.
我女朋友在这里工作
My girlfriend works here.
她在那边呢
She's right over...
就这一次 我破例跟我的顾客约会
This one time only, I'm gonna break my rule.
我们明晚约会吧
Let's go out tomorrow night!
太棒了
Sweet!
哦 糟糕了
Oh, shoot!
我明天要上班 擦
I have to work tomorrow. Ugh!
嘿 头脑风暴
Hey! Brainstorm!
不如我们在这儿约会
What if we just have our date here,
也许去那个专属包间
maybe in the Champagne Room?
那可是我们地儿
That was our spot.
嗨 帅哥 想看我跳个舞吗
Hey, gorgeous, You want a dance?
又是个圈套么
Is it a jig?
如果是的话 该结束了
'Cause if so, it's up.
抱歉 我的情感跟麻辣老师
Sorry, I only had the last verse
麻辣老师最后一句歌词是"噢 我的天哪"
最后一句一样 刚那算啥
of "Hot For Teacher" To work on that. What was that?
你用昨天对我说的话去糊弄那个男的
You laid exactly the same line on that guy that you did on me!
小甜心 那些话
Sweetie, that is just something
我只对那些容易上当的二货们说
I say to these gullible losers here.
他们每次都会相信哟
They fall for it every time.
一帮笨蛋
Bunch of losers!
噢 天哪 经理又来了
Oh, gosh, manager again.
他看着我好像在说
He's looking at me like,
卡玛 你们为啥不去
"Karma, why aren't you booking more time
专属套房呆会呢
in the Champagne Room?"
当然没问题了
Well, we'll show him.
不 你又在玩我
No! You're playing me again!
你的谎话还真是张口就来啊
And you're not even trying hard!
经理压根就不在 你在指一个盆栽
There's no manager there; You're pointing at a fern!
泰德是对的
Ted was right.
我敢说他一定在家 嘲笑我有多二
I bet he's home right now, laughing at how dumb I am.
我这是不是报应呢 当然了
Did I deserve this? Absolutely.
哥也说过些无耻的谎话
I have told some outrageous lies.
我曾告诉别的妞
I have told women I was famous,
我是个有名的战时英雄
a war hero,
和我滚床单的话 就能够治愈近视
that sex with me would cure their nearsightedness.
巴尼 是你
Barney?!
你对我做的这些 可能都是我应得的报应
I probably deserved everything you did to me and more.
但是我一直在努力
But I have been trying,
努力去成为一个更好的人
and trying hard to be a better person.
谢谢你刚让我明白了
Thanks for showing me
我原来的生活方式没错
I had it right before.
这么说吧 很抱歉让你感觉有点压抑
Look, I'm sorry we made you feel a little suffocated,
但是你真的要偷偷溜走吗
but were you really just gonna sneak away?
我只是  我真的很想念城里
Well, it's just... I really miss the city.
我也知道你们很爱这里 这挺好的
I know you guys love it here, and that's fine,
我们才不爱这里呢
We don't love it here!
啥
What?
拜托 罗宾
Come on, Robin,
你没看到这里的生活是什么样的啊
what kind of life is this?
去参加无聊的凯纳斯特纸牌联赛
Going to canasta tournaments
去高中运动场看所谓的曲棍球季后赛
and high school field hockey playoffs?
噢 我觉得北贝拉莫会得冠军的
Oh, I think North Bellmore can take state.
看看苏菲的踝关节  哥表示怀疑
With Sophie's ankle? Doubtful.
好吧 要是你们俩不开心的话
Okay, but if you two are so unhappy,
为什么不直接搬回曼哈顿呢
why don't you just move back to Manhattan?
因为郊区对宝宝比较好啊
Because the suburbs are better for the baby.
谁说的 连你们俩都住着不开心的地方
Who says? Who says any place is better for the baby
会真的对宝宝好吗
if you two are unhappy in it?
不 不 我们现在就住在这儿了
No, no, we live here now.
其实呢 这个地方
And, you know, this place
也没有那么糟啦
wouldn't seem so bad if...
要是我们有一个朋友也搬来这里了的话
we got one of our friends to move out here.
噢 伙计们
Oh, guys...
噢
Oh...
姐自焚也不会留在这儿的
I would rather set myself on fire.
第二天早上 巴尼知道了即使在这个
The next morning, Barney learned that even in
人口八百万的城市 他也躲不开卡玛(报应)
a city of eight million people, there's no escaping Karma.
噢
Oh.
噢 嗨
Oh, hey.
抱歉 哥不能讲话 经理盯着呢
Sorry, can't talk; manager's watching.
听着 要是伤害到你的感情的话
Look, I am sorry
我很抱歉 这只是份工作
if I hurt your feelings; it's a job.
是吗 哥的工作
Yeah, well, at my job,
我们不会为了钱而让别人心碎
we don't rip out people's hearts for money.
我们短暂的支持过朝鲜的一个
My company briefly backed a lab in North Korea
令人心碎的实验室 但是后来还是卖了它
which did, but we sold it!
你知道么 我在这个俱乐部工作了一年
You know, I've worked at that club for a year.
你一直在那儿
You practically live there,
但我们约会时 你都没认出我来
and you didn't even recognize me the night we went out.
你那套小可怜的受害者形象骗不了我
You can't pretend to be some hurt little victim with me.
我了解你
I know you.
好吧 当然你了解我
Well, of course you do.
一些事情我只告诉过你一个人
I told you things I don't tell anybody.
我对你是坦白的
I was honest with you.
切 我不相信你有一个同性恋的黑人哥哥
Yeah, because I believe you have a gay black brother,
一个孤单到快被自己熏熟的朋友
a friend lonely enough to smoke his own meat
还有个新浪潮乐队的粉儿的老妈
and that your mom was a groupie for Supertramp.
他们以她命的乐队的名
They named their band for her!
这些你竟然都记得
You remembered all that?
好吧 是的 我的意思是说
Well, yeah. I mean,
你的故事比放了八千遍的
you're more interesting than the lyrics
“往我身上倒糖”的歌词要有意思
to "Pour Some Sugar On Me" For the 8,000th time.
你知道么 这很奇怪
You know, it's funny.
几乎我见过的每个女人
Almost every woman I've ever met was wrong
都错误地给了我一次机会
to give me a chance.
你却是第一个因为没给我机会而做错的
You're the first woman who's wrong not to.
大杯黑咖啡
Large black coffee...
还有他点的东西
and whatever he's having.
我一起付
It's on me.
我也要一杯咖啡
The same.
谢谢
Thank you.
别客气
You're welcome.
再请1700杯咖啡 我俩就扯平了
1,700 more of these and we're even.
呀 这首歌刚刚结束了
Uh, the song just ended.
是不是意味着你要走了
That mean you got to get going?
不
No.
你有空和我坐一会吗
Do you have time to sit with me?
不知道 我的表在你那儿
I don't know. You're wearing my watch.
陶艺 现在你迷上陶艺了
Pottery. Now you're making pottery.
我需要一个花瓶
I needed a new vase...
和几个盘子
and some plates.
以及几个碗
And bowls.
好吧 我的瓷器柜子设计得不好
The china cabinet I built had some design flaws.
为什么你不把这改成一间客房
Why don't you just turn this into a guest room?
客房
A guest room?
你的意思是一间等待着
You mean a room ready and waiting
不属于这的人的房间
for someone who isn't there?
还是一间提醒我还是单身的房间
A room devoted to reminding me that I'm still alone?
不 我不需要那样
Yeah, I don't need that.
泰德 无论你放多少东西到这个房间
Ted, no matter how many things you put in this room...
我都在这儿
I'll still be here.
嗨
Hey.
Hey!
请进吧
Come on in.
谢了
Thanks.
噢 额 谢谢你帮我打包我余下的东西
Oh, um, thanks for packing up the rest of my stuff.
小意思 额你想喝点儿咖啡么
No problem. Uh, you want some coffee?
-额 当然 -是呵 -是的
Uh, sure. Yeah? Yeah.
那啥 最近怎么样呀
So, how are things?
-挺好的 你呢 -我好的不得了
Good! You? Great!
你知道么 这杯子是我亲手做的
You know, I actually made this mug.
哦 是么 噢 天哪
Oh, yeah? Oh! Yeah. Oh!
噢 不好意思 咖啡太浓烈了
Yeah, sorry, coffee's a little strong.
在马修和莉莉那住的怎么样呀
How was your stay with Marshall and Lily?
额 有点儿怪怪的
Uh... A little weird.
其实他们不喜欢长岛
They're not loving Long Island.
喔
Oh.
我想他们心底还是意识到
I think deep down, they realize
他们不适合那儿
it just... isn't a good fit.
有时候要承认这一点很难
It's hard to admit that sometimes.
确实
Sure is.
不过我想最好还是要面对这些 继续自己的人生
But I guess it's better to face it and move on
而不该强求那些本不属于自己的事物 对吧
than try to force something that just isn't meant to be, right?
我也这么觉得
I think so.
那么 你觉得你要怎样
So, what do you think
来处理我原来的房间
you're gonna do with my old room?
我还没完全想好
Haven't really thought about it.
噢
Oh!
谁稀罕曼哈顿啊
Who needs Manhattan?
是啊
Yeah.
恩 是泰德 他想知道
Hmm, it's Ted. He wants to know
我们想不想去市里聚一聚
if we want to hang out in the city.
下一班列车九分钟走
The next train leaves in nine minutes.
亲爱的莉莉和马修 我不知道你们是否知道
Dear Lily and Marshall, I don't know if you know this,
我从来没把你们的名字从租约上删掉
but I never took your names off the lease.
而今天 我把我的名字删了
Well, today I took my name off it.
这个公寓现在属于你们了
The apartment is now yours.
我想我也找到
And I think I finally figured out the best thing
处置罗宾房间的最好方法了
to do with Robin's old room.
对我来说 这个地方已经有鬼影缠绕了
See, for me, this place has begun to feel a little haunted.
开始 我以为我是被的罗宾缠绕着
At first, I thought it was haunted by Robin,
但是现在 我觉得其实我是被自己缠绕着
but now I think it was haunted by me.
直到有新生活开始 那些小鬼才能不闹腾了
Well, no ghost is at peace until it finally moves on.
我需要改变
I need a change.
而且我觉得你们也需要
And I think you do, too.
这个公寓现在需要新生命
This apartment needs some new life.
所以请把我们的旧家装扮成你俩的新家
So, please, make our old home your new home.
它现在再也不会被幽灵缠绕了
It is now ghost-free.
爱你们的 泰德
Love, Ted.